shereadstruth.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - She Reads Truth : She Reads Truth

The She Reads Truth Bible and Devotional App and She Reads Truth web site are owned and operated by She Reads Truth, LLC. We know you care how information about you is used and shared. We care about that stuff, too! We hope the following statements will help you understand how She Reads Truth will collect, use and protect the information you provide to us on our app.

**What we collect and how we use it**

**Information you provide  
**You are not required to create an account in order to use the She Reads Truth App or Web Site, but you do have the option of providing personal information (including your name, email address and web site URL) for commenting purposes. This information is stored on your device solely for the purpose of allowing you to comment on daily devotional posts without having to enter your information for each comment.

**Unique Device ID and GPS location  
**When you access the She Reads Truth App or Web Site, we may collect your Unique Device ID (‘UDID’) and/or IP address and/or GPS location. We use this information to provide a tailored experience for you. The information is collected in order to determine the aggregate number of unique devices using our service or parts of our service, to track total usage, analyze data, and communicate with you more effectively. We do not share any personally identifiable information with third parties in association with your UDID or GPS location without your explicit permission.

**Log information  
**When you use the She Reads Truth App or Web Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends when you visit one of our websites. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. This information is used solely for the purposes of analyzing usage of the app so that we may improve its function and better serve our community of users.

**User communications  
**Personal information or requests that you submit via [shereadstruth.com](http://shereadstruth.com/) or the Feedback button in the She Reads Truth App will be sent to a site administrator. A site administrator and/or members of the She Reads Truth administrative team will have access to this information. When you send email or other communication to any She Reads Truth, LLC owned website, we may retain those communications to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

**Third party sites  
**This Privacy Policy applies only to sites and apps that are owned and operated by She Reads Truth, LLC. She Reads Truth, LLC cannot regulate other sites linked from within our various web sites and services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. You should familiarize yourself with their unique Privacy Policies, should you choose to visit their sites.

**How do we use your information?**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, like commenting, we ask you to provide personal information. If She Reads Truth would like to use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. You may decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case we may not be able to provide those services to you.

**How do we protect your information?**

She Reads Truth, LLC does not share your personal information with other institutions outside of She Reads Truth, LLC without your explicit consent. She Reads Truth, LLC may share your personal information only if it has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms Of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of She Reads Truth, LLC, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. She Reads Truth, LLC takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data, including internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. Unless explicit permission is obtained from you, She Reads Truth, LLC restricts access to personal information to its employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Data Integrity**

She Reads Truth, LLC takes reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use any She Reads Truth, LLC service, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate service purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users’ personal information.

**Enforcement**

She Reads Truth, LLC periodically reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints regarding privacy issues, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between She Reads Truth, LLC and an individual.

**Questions**

Any questions about the privacy policy can be directed to: hello@shereadstruth.com.
